db.questions.insertMany([
  {
  Category:"Sports",
  Difficulty: "Easy",
  Type: "Identification",
  Question: "How many players per team are there in court in handball?",
  Answer: "7",
  choiceA: "6",
  choiceB: "7",
  choiceC: "8",
  choiceD: "9"
  }
]);

db.questions.insertMany([{
  Category: "Science",
  Difficulty: "Easy",
  Type: "True or False",
  Question: "Is this true?",
  Answer: 'True',
  choiceA: 'True',
  choiceB: 'False',
  choiceC: '',
  choiceD: ''
}]);

db.questions.insertMany([
{
Category:"Sports",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question: "How many players per team are there in court in handball?",
Answer: "7",
choiceA: "6",
choiceB: "7",
choiceC: "8",
choiceD: "9"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"How many squares are there in a chess board?",
Answer: "64",
choiceA: "48",
choiceB: "56",
choiceC: "64",
choiceD: "72"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What is the name given to the NFL final?",
Answer: "Super Bowl",
choiceA: "Super Bowl",
choiceB: "World Cup",
choiceC: "Wimbledon",
choiceD: "The Masters"
},
{
Category:"Sports",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"When did the FIFA World Cup take place in the USA?",
Answer: "1994",
choiceA: "1991",
choiceB: "1992",
choiceC: "1993",
choiceD: "1994"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"When will be the next Olympic Games?",
Answer: "2020",
choiceA: "2018",
choiceB: "2019",
choiceC: "2020",
choiceD: "2021"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"The tiger Hodori was the mascot of which Olympic Games?",
Answer: "Seoul 88 Olympic Games",
choiceA: "Seoul 84 Olympic Games",
choiceB: "Seoul 86 Olympic Games",
choiceC: "Seoul 88 Olympic Games",
choiceD: "Seoul 90 Olympic Games"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Swords are used in which of the following martial arts?",
Answer: "Ninjutsu",
choiceA: "Ninjutsu",
choiceB: "Chijutsu",
choiceC: "Jujutsu",
choiceD: "Chajutsu"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What year were the first modern Olympics Games held?",
Answer: "1896",
choiceA: "1894",
choiceB: "1896",
choiceC: "1898",
choiceD: "1900"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What country is Taekwondo originally from?",
Answer: "Korea",
choiceA: "China",
choiceB: "Japan",
choiceC: "Thailand",
choiceD: "Korea"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who won the Formula One World’s Driver Championship in 2005 and 2006?",
Answer: "Fernando Alonso",
choiceA: "Paavo Nurmi",
choiceB: "Fernando Alonso",
choiceC: "Mark Spitz",
choiceD: "Carl Lewis"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"From which country is the athlete Maria Mutola, who won her eighth world title in Paris in 2003?",
Answer: "Mozambique",
choiceA: "Turkmenistan",
choiceB: "Pakistan",
choiceC: "Dubai",
choiceD: "Mozambique"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Anna Kournikova won the doubles competition of the Australian Open of 1999. What swiss player was her partner?",
Answer: "Martina Hingis",
choiceA: "Mal Meninga",
choiceB: "Mal Meningo",
choiceC: "Martina Hingis",
choiceD: "Martina Hingos"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"How many goals did Germany score in the 2014 World Cup Against Brazil?",
Answer: "7",
choiceA: "4",
choiceB: "5",
choiceC: "6",
choiceD: "7"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"How many games were disputed in the longest match in the history of Wimbledon?",
Answer: "183",
choiceA: "183",
choiceB: "184",
choiceC: "185",
choiceD: "186"
},
{
Category: "Sports",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Where were the first Pan American Games celebrated, in 1951?",
Answer: "Buenos Aires",
choiceA: "Canada",
choiceB: "Kazakhstan",
choiceC: "Buenos Aires",
choiceD: "Argentina"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who played the character of Edward Scissorhands?",
Answer: "Johnny Depp",
choiceA: "Andrew Garfield",
choiceB: "Johnny Depp",
choiceC: "Morgan Freeman",
choiceD: "Hugh Ackman"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"The 2014 film Maleficent is based on which story?",
Answer: "Sleeping Beauty",
choiceA: "Snow White and The Seven Dwarves",
choiceB: "Thumbelina",
choiceC: "Sleeping Beauty",
choiceD: "The Little Mermaid"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Who wrote the famous opera-rock song ‘ Bohemian Rhapsody’?",
Answer: "Freddy Mercury",
choiceA: "Paul Rogers",
choiceB: "Freddy Mercury",
choiceC: "Bryan Myers",
choiceD: "Led Zeppelin"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Who was Naruto's first sensei?",
Answer: "Iruka",
choiceA: "Kakashi",
choiceB: "Jiraya",
choiceC: "Guy",
choiceD: "Iruka"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What color is the Little Mermaid's tail?",
Answer: "Green",
choiceA: "Violet",
choiceB: "Green",
choiceC: "Pink",
choiceD: "Blue"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What US president did Forrest Gump not meet?",
Answer: "Eisenhower",
choiceA: "Eisenhower",
choiceB: "Washington",
choiceC: "Johnson",
choiceD: "Hoover"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"With whom of the following was Michael Jackson married to?",
Answer: "Lisa Marie Presley",
choiceA: "Eliza Maria Presley",
choiceB: "Lisa Marie Presley",
choiceC: "Jira Angel",
choiceD: "Dannah Esperanza"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What year did ‘Thriller’ come out?",
Answer: "1982",
choiceA: "1980",
choiceB: "1981",
choiceC: "1982",
choiceD: "1983"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What year did the Red Hot Chili Peppers release their first album?",
Answer: "1984",
choiceA: "1984",
choiceB: "1985",
choiceC: "1986",
choiceD: "1987"
},
{
Category:"Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What’s the name of the cat that wants to eat the smurfs?",
Answer: "Azrael",
choiceA: "Lux",
choiceB: "Azrael",
choiceC: "Ezikiel",
choiceD: "Bob"
},
{
Category: "Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What was the address Dori was looking for on Finding Nemo?",
Answer: "P Sherman 42 Wallaby Way Sidney",
choiceA: "P Shermen 43 Wallaby Way Sidney",
choiceB: "P Shermen 42 Wallaby Way Sidney",
choiceC: "P Sherman 42 Wallaby Way Sidney",
choiceD: "P Sherman 43 Wallaby Way Sidney"},
{
Category: "Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"How many letters did Noah write to Allie in The Notebook?",
Answer: "365",
choiceA: "361",
choiceB: "363",
choiceC: "365",
choiceD: "367"
},
{
Category: "Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Who won the Academy Award for Best Actor in a Supporting Role in 2004?",
Answer: "Morgan Freeman",
choiceA: "Hugh Ackman",
choiceB: "Morgan Freeman",
choiceC: "Robert Downey Jr.",
choiceD: "Jackie Chan"
},
{
Category: "Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What did Jack Nicholson play in the film ‘Prizzi’s Honour’?",
Answer: "Mafia Hitman",
choiceA: "Mafia Hitman",
choiceB: "Information Broker",
choiceC: "Boxer",
choiceD: "Assasin"
},
{

Category: "Entertainment",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Which actor portrayed Clark Kent in the movie ‘Man of Steel’?",
Answer: "Henry Cavill",
choiceA: "Dean Cain",
choiceB: "Channing Tatum",
choiceC: "Tim Daly",
choiceD: "Henry Cavill"
},
{
Category:"Science:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What does a glaucoma provoke if its not treated?",
Answer: "Blindness",
choiceA: "Deafness",
choiceB: "Tremors",
choiceC: "Nausea",
choiceD: "Blindness"
},
{
Category:"Science:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Which two common household items have a violent chemical reaction when combined?",
Answer: "Sodium bicarbonate and vinegar",
choiceA: "Sodium bicarbonate and Ethanol",
choiceB: "Vinegar and Sodium Hydroxide",
choiceC: "Sodium bicarbonate and vinegar",
choiceD: "Calcium carbonate and Sodium bicarbonate"
},
{
Category:"Science:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Au is an abbreviation for which chemical element?",Answer: "Gold",choiceA: "Gold",choiceB: "Silver",choiceC: "Copper",choiceD: "Iron"
},
{
Category:"Science:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"How is tooth cavity usually fixed?",Answer: "By filling it",choiceA: "By extracting it",choiceB: "By cleaning it",choiceC: "By replacing it with dentures",choiceD: "By filling it"
},
{
Category:"Science:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Which is the name of the most extended artery of the human body?",Answer: "Aorta",choiceA: "Aorta",choiceB: "Axilla",choiceC: "Arteria Dorsalis",choiceD: "Thoracic"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"When are young elephants considered to be adults?",Answer: "12 to 15 years old",choiceA: "12 to 15 years old",choiceB: "13 to 16 years old",choiceC: "11 to 14 years old",choiceD: "10 to 13 years old"},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"Which part of the eye responds to light?",Answer: "Retina",choiceA: "Sclera",choiceB: "Cornea",choiceC: "Retina",choiceD: "Iris"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What's the colostrum?",Answer: "The first breast milk",choiceA: "The first period",choiceB: "The first breast milk",choiceC: "The first pregnancy",choiceD: "The first ejaculation"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What is plastic made of?",Answer: "Oil",choiceA: "Leaves",choiceB: "Oil",choiceC: "Rocks",choiceD: "Wood"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What does vexillology study?",Answer: "Study of Flags",choiceA: "Study of Glands",choiceB: "Study of Worms",choiceC: "Study of Tides",choiceD: "Study of Flags"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What's the name of the chronic mood disorder that alternates periods of hypomanic symptoms with periods of mild depression?",Answer: "Cyclothymia",choiceA: "Bipolar disorder",choiceB: "Major Depression",choiceC: "Cyclothymia",choiceD: "Dysthymia"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What prevents virus replication?",Answer: "Interferons",choiceA: "Algesia",choiceB: "Anodonta",choiceC: "Dorsalon",choiceD: "Interferons"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What does a speleologist study?",Answer: "Caves",choiceA: "Sun",choiceB: "Caves",choiceC: "Flags",choiceD: "Waves"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"What is aboulia?",Answer: "A decrease of motivation",choiceA: "A decrease of emotion",choiceB: "A decrease of motivation",choiceC: "A sudden decrease of happiness",choiceD: "A decrease of energy"
},
{
Category: "Science",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:	"The Statue of Liberty is covered in what material?",Answer: "Copper",choiceA: "Lead",choiceB: "Cadium",choiceC: "Copper",choiceD: "Scandium"
},
{
Category:"Geography:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What are the colors of the Philippines flag?",Answer:"Blue, Red, Yellow and White",choiceA:"Red and White",choiceB:"Red, White and Black",choiceC:"Blue, Red, Yellow and White",choiceD:"Red, Blue, and White"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What country is famous for the maple tree?",Answer:"Canada",choiceA:"USA",choiceB:"UK",choiceC:"Philippines",choiceD:"Canada"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What’s the meaning of D.C in Washington D.C?",Answer: "District of Columbia",choiceA:"District of Columbia",choiceB:"District of Cambodia",choiceC:"District of Canada",choiceD:"District of Caine"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What is the color of the Japanese Flag?",Answer:"White and Red",choiceA:"Red and Yellow",choiceB: "White and Red",choiceC:"Red and Black",choiceD: "White and Black"},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"When is the Spring in the Southern Hemisphere?",Answer:"September to December",choiceA:"December to March",choiceB:"March to June",choiceC:"June to September",choiceD:"September to December"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Which of the following countries has the highest life expectancy?",Answer:"Japan",choiceA:"China",choiceB:"Japan",choiceC:"South Korea",choiceD:"North Korea"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Where can you find the largest flower, Rafflesia?",Answer:"Malaysia",choiceA: "Indonesia",choiceB:"Singapore",choiceC:"Hong Kong",choiceD:"Malaysia"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Taiwan is also known as?",Answer:"Formosa Island",choiceA:"Formosa Island",choiceB:"Fragrant Harbour",choiceC:"Spice Island",choiceD:"Insulinde"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Which of the following countries does NOT have red in its flag?",Answer:"Saudi Arabia",choiceA:"China",choiceB:"Nepal",choiceC:"Saudi Arabia",choiceD:"Philippines"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Which of these is NOT one of the ‘New Wonders of the World’?",
Answer:"Eiffel Tower",choiceA:"Eiffel Tower",choiceB:"Christ the Redeemer Statue",choiceC:"Machu Picchu",choiceD:"Taj Majal"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What country is the last to see the sun set?",Answer:"Samoa",choiceA:"Hawaii",choiceB:"New Zealand",choiceC:"Ecuador",choiceD:"Samoa"
},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What element does Argentina owe its name to?",Answer:"Silver",choiceA:"Silver",choiceB:"Gold",choiceC:"Arsenic",choiceD:"Astatine"},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What is the real name of the Japanese Cat Island, famous for its huge cat population?",Answer:"Tashirojima",choiceA:"Inujima",choiceB:"Okunoshima",choiceC:"Tashirojima",choiceD:"Miyagi Zao"},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Where is the Capoeira dance from?",Answer: "Mafia Hitman",choiceA:"Brazil",choiceB:"Africa",choiceC:"India",choiceD:"Hawaii"},
{
Category: "Geography",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Which is the most populated city of Turkey?",Answer:"Istanbul",choiceA:"Ankara",choiceB:"Izmir",choiceC:"Antalya",choiceD: "Istanbul"
},
{
Category:"History:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who founded Playboy magazine?",Answer: "Hugh Hefner",choiceA: "Hugh Hefner",choiceB: "Henry Hudson",choiceC: "John Muir",choiceD: "Kit Carson"
},
{
Category:"History:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who held the famous I have a dream speech in 1963?",Answer: "Martin Luther King",choiceA: "Abraham Lincoln",choiceB: "Thomas Jefferson",choiceC: "Martin Luther King",choiceD: "Franklin Roosevelt"
},
{
Category:"History:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who was Britain’s longest-reigning monarch?",Answer: "Victoria",choiceA: "Anne",choiceB: "William",choiceC: "George",choiceD: "Victoria"
},
{
Category:"History:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Which was the weapon of choice for Samurais?",Answer: "Katana",choiceA: "Kama",choiceB: "Katana",choiceC: "Kiseru",choiceD: "Tekkan and Hachiwari"
},
{
Category:"History:",
Difficulty: "Easy",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who was the first president of the United States?",Answer: "George Washington",choiceA: "George Washington",choiceB: "Abraham Lincoln",choiceC: "George Bush",choiceD: "Theodore Roosevelt"
},
{
Category:"History",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What was Sally Ride the first American woman to do?",Answer: "Go into outer space",choiceA: "Win an olympic medal",choiceB: "Go into outer space",choiceC: "Fly solo around the world.",choiceD: "Receive a pilot's license."
},
{
Category:"History",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What year did the Titanic sink?",Answer: "1912",choiceA: "1911",choiceB: "1910",choiceC: "1913",choiceD: "1912"
},
{
Category:"History",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What Wonder of the Ancient World was in what is Iraq today?",Answer: "Hanging gardens of Babylon",choiceA: "The Abbasid Palace",choiceB: "Ziggurat of Ur",choiceC: "Aqar Quf/ Dur-Kurigalzu",choiceD: "Hanging gardens of babylon"
},
{
Category:"History",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Where was Pearl Harbor, the military based attacked by the Japanese army was located?",Answer: "Hawaii",choiceA: "Israel",choiceB: "Philippines",choiceC: "Hawaii",choiceD: "America"
},
{
Category:"History",
Difficulty: "Medium",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What starts with ‘Four score and seven years ago?",Answer: "Gettsburg Address",choiceA: "Gettsburg Address",choiceB: "We Shall Fight on the Beaches",choiceC: "Surrender Speech",choiceD: "Farewell to Baseball Address"
},
{
Category: "History",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What country did USA purchase Alaska from?",Answer: "Russia",choiceA: "Cuba",choiceB: "Russia",choiceC: "Argentina",choiceD: "Venezuela"
},
{
Category: "History",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What was one of the names given to the atomic bombs of Hiroshima and Nagasaki?",Answer: "Little Boy",choiceA: "Little Boy",choiceB: "Little Man",choiceC: "Little Guy",choiceD: "Fat Boy"
},
{
Category: "History",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"Who discovered the sea route to India?",Answer: "Vasco Da Gama",choiceA: "Narendra Modi",choiceB: "Vasco Da Gama",choiceC: "Aamir Khan",choiceD: "Virat Kohli"
},
{
Category: "History",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"What was the name of Adolf Hitler’s wife?",Answer: "Eva",choiceA: "Evie",choiceB: "Eve",choiceC: "Evelyn",choiceD: "Eva"
},
{
Category: "History",
Difficulty: "Difficult",
Type: "Multiple Choice",
Question:"The Philippines was discovered by Europeans in what year?",Answer: "1521",choiceA: "1521",choiceB: "1522",choiceC: "1523",choiceD: "1524"
}
]);
